RISM Collections at New York University Conferences Guide to the Records of New Perspectives on Caribbean Studies: Toward the 21st Century and Prospects for Caribbean Basin Integration (Conference held at Hunter College, CUNY, August 28-September 1, 1984) RISM RG 16 (j)
New York University Archives
- Series XVI. Audio and Video Recordings, August 1984 - March 1985
  - Video Tape Shelf List
    - "Caribbean Conference, Playhouse Session, Michael Manley, Camera 3, Tape 2 (from the balcony)", undated (Box 27, Reel 68768/19)
    - "Caribbean Conference, Playhouse Session Awards, includes Lamming [George Lamming] Speech contained in Tape 4, Camera 1", undated (Box 27, Reel 68768/20)
    - "Original Tape 4A, Camera 1, 25 min.", undated (Box 27, Reel 68768/21)
    - "Migration (cont.) Historical Overview, Original, Tape 4, Camera 2, 25 min.", undated (Box 27, Reel 68768/22)
    - "Migration (cont.) Historical Overview, Original, Tape 5, Camera 1, 39 min., Beginning of Caribbean Crisis and Response", undated (Box 27, Reel 68768/23)
    - "Migration (cont.) Historical Overview, Original, Tape 5A, Camera 2, 39 min.; beginning of "Caribbean Crisis and Response", undated (Box 27, Reel 68768/24)
    - "Haitian Interview (cont.), Original, Tape 3, Camera 1, Migration", undated (Box 27, Reel 68768/25)
    - "Haiti (1st part), Migration (1st part), Original, Tape 3A, Camera 2", undated (Box 27, Reel 68768/26)
  - Digibeta versions of tapes 1-26 and DVDs 1-26 (Box 29)
    - Rism Digibeta tape 1 (Box 28, Reel 1)
    - Rism Digibeta tape 2 (Box 28, Reel 2)
    - Rism Digibeta tape 3 (Box 28, Reel 3)
    - Rism digibeta tape 4 (Box 28, Reel 4)
    - Rism digibeta tape 5 (Box 28, Reel 5)
    - Rism digibeta tape 6 (Box 28, Reel 6)
    - Rism digibeta tape 7 (Box 28, Reel 7)
    - Rism digibeta tape 8 (Box 28, Reel 8)
    - Rism digibeta tape 9 (Box 28, Reel 9)
    - Rism digibeta tape 10 (Box 28, Reel 10)
    - Rism digibeta tape 11 (Box 28, Reel 11)
    - Rism digibeta tape 12 (Box 28, Reel 12)
    - Rism digibeta tape 13 (Box 28, Reel 13)
    - Rism digibeta tape 14 (Box 28, Reel 14)
    - Rism digibeta tape 15 (Box 28, Reel 15)
    - Rism digibeta tape 16 (Box 28, Reel 16)
    - Rism digibeta tape 17 (Box 29, Reel 17)
    - Rism digibeta tape 18 (Box 29, Reel 18)
    - Rism digibeta tape 19 (Box 29, Reel 19)
    - Rism digibeta tape 20 (Box 29, Reel 20)
    - Rism digibeta tape 21 (Box 29, Reel 21)
    - Rism digibeta tape 22 (Box 29, Reel 22)
    - Rism digibeta tape 23 (Box 29, Reel 23)
    - Rism digibeta tape 24 (Box 29, Reel 24)
    - Rism digibeta tape 25 (Box 29, Reel 25)
    - Rism digibeta tape 26 (Box 29, Reel 26)
- Appendix
  - Presented Papers, 1984; 1.0 boxes Duplicate papers as presented at the Conference (Box 30)